<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Recipes on Cucumber Sandwiches And Tea</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/</link><description>Recent content in Recipes on Cucumber Sandwiches And Tea</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>3 kinds of dip</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-08-xx_3-kinds-of-dip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-08-xx_3-kinds-of-dip/</guid><description>( we forgot to take pictures :( )
Ingredients 1 tomato 3 tbsp. mayonnaise salt, pepper Directions Boil water. Put the tomato in the boiled water for a few minutes. Peel the tomato. Cut the tomato into small cubes, removing the seeds. Mix everything together. Ingredients 5 cornichons 3 tbsp. mayonnaise parsley salt, pepper Directions Cut the cornichons into small cubes. Mix everything together.</description></item><item><title>Avocado Wasabi Salad</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_avocado-wasabi-salad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_avocado-wasabi-salad/</guid><description>We found this delicious recipe for a salad: Avocado Wasabi Salad.
We didn&amp;rsquo;t have any broccoli the first time we made it, but it was still great. The amount of dressing is a bit much and we still have some in the fridge, so next time we&amp;rsquo;re probably only going to make half the dressing.</description></item><item><title>Chocolate lava cake</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_chocolate-lava-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_chocolate-lava-cake/</guid><description>I accidentally stumbled across this recipe the other day and had to try it: Chocolate Lava Cake.
It tastes wonderful. I want to make it again, but I probably shouldn&amp;rsquo;t.</description></item><item><title>Congo Bars</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-06-xx_congo-bars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-06-xx_congo-bars/</guid><description>Ingredients 150 g butter, softened 3 eggs 200 g brown sugar (1 cup) 1 packet vanilla sugar (about 3 tsp.) 350 g flour (3 cups) 2 1/2 tsp. baking powder 1/2 teaspoon salt 100 g chocolate Directions Chop the chocolate finely. Preheat the oven to 180 °C. Combine butter, vanilla sugar and brown sugar using a mixer until blended. Add eggs, one at a time to sugar mixture, mixing on low in between each addition.</description></item><item><title>Courgette soup</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-07-xx_courgette-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-07-xx_courgette-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients 400g courgette 1 small onion 2 small potatoes olive oil 250 ml vegetable broth 3 tbsp lime juice (to taste) salt, pepper 250 ml butter milk Directions Cut the courgette, onion and small potatoes into small pieces. Heat the olive oil in a pan. Saute the onion in the olive oil briefly, then add courgette and potatoes. Add the vegetable broth and let simmer until the potatoes are soft.</description></item><item><title>Cucumber Sandwiches</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_cucumber-sandwiches/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_cucumber-sandwiches/</guid><description>Step 1: Toast
Ingredients 100 ml water 12 g fresh yeast 18 g salt 250 ml milk 500 g flour 2 tsp. baking powder 20 g sugar 20 g starch 30 g butter Directions In a small bowl mix water, yeast and salt. Stir well and leave for at least 30 minutes. I usually leave it overnight. Add the milk to the yeast mixture. In a large bowl mix the flour, baking powder, sugar, starch and butter.</description></item><item><title>Cup-O'-Ccino</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_cup-o-ccino-with-liquid-chocolate-core/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_cup-o-ccino-with-liquid-chocolate-core/</guid><description>Ingredients 120 g margarine&amp;lt; 100 g sugar 2 eggs (large) 180 g flour 2 tsp. baking powder 6 tbsp. espresso 150 g chocolate Directions Chop 50 g of the chocolate into small pieces. Place margarine and sugar in a large bowl. Mix until fluffy. Add the eggs one by one, beating the mixture until it is smooth each time. Preheat the oven to 180° C. Mix the flour and baking powder and stir into the bowl.</description></item><item><title>Enchiladas</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_enchiladas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_enchiladas/</guid><description>Ingredients 500 g broccoli 250 g ricotta 1-2 cloves garlic 1 tsp cumin 100 g grated cheese (Gouda) 1 egg 6 tortillas 1 tsp. salt 1 tsp. pepper Directions Cut the broccoli into small pieces. We cooked the broccoli for 3-4 minutes, but this is probably not necessary. In a large bowl mix the broccoli, ricotta, cumin, garlic and 50 g of the cheese. Stir in the egg and the salt and pepper.</description></item><item><title>Guacamole</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_guacamole/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_guacamole/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 avocado (very ripe!) 6 tbsp. lime juice 2 tbsp. olive oil 2 cloves of garlic 1 onion salt &amp;amp; pepper chili powder 1 tomato Directions Peel the avocado. Place in a blender with 3 tbsp. lime juice and 1 tbsp. olive oil. Chop the garlic and onion. Also place in the blender. Add spices to taste. (salt, pepper, chili) Blend! Chop the tomato. Place in the blender.</description></item><item><title>Hirsepfanne</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_hirse-pfanne/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_hirse-pfanne/</guid><description>We made this german recipe: Hirse-Pfanne.I didn&amp;rsquo;t add the whipped cream to the yoghurt and it was very good that way too.
It seems that &amp;lsquo;Hirse&amp;rsquo; translates to millet, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find very many english recipes with millet. Can you buy millet in England or another english-speaking country?</description></item><item><title>Honey-Balsamico Sauce</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-06-xx_honey-balsamico-sauce/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-06-xx_honey-balsamico-sauce/</guid><description>Ingredients 3 shallots 1 apple 1 tsp. oil 20 g butter 20 g flour 200 ml vegetable broth 3 tbsp. balsamico 2 tbsp. honey 1 twig rosemary Directions Chop the shallots into thin rings. Cut the apple into small pieces. Chop the rosemary finely. Heat the oil in a pan. Sweat the shallots and apple until the shallots are lucent. Set the shallots and apple to the side.</description></item><item><title>Kaiser rolls</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_kaiser-rolls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_kaiser-rolls/</guid><description>Ingredients 250 ml water 10 g fresh yeast (or 1 packet dried yeast) 1 tsp sugar 1 tsp. salt 450 g flour 20 g butter 1 tbsp yoghurt (optional) 1 egg 3 tbsp. milk Directions Crumble the yeast into the water and mix until dissolved. Add the sugar and salt. Leave it for at least half an hour in a warm place. Place flour in a large mixing bowl.</description></item><item><title>Kimchi Udon</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/udon-noodles/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/udon-noodles/</guid><description>Ingredients 500 g Udon (fresh) 1 can Kimchi 2 tsp Gochujang 5 tbsp Butter Garnish Sesame Seeds 1 egg yellow per plate spring onion Directions Drain the kimchi, retaining the liquid. In a frying pan heat up 2 tbsp of the butter and add the kimchi and gochujang. Fry for about 4 minutes on medium heat. Add the liquid from the kimchi, remaining butter and the udon noodles and cook for another 2-3 minutes.</description></item><item><title>Kumquat Muffins</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_kumquat-muffins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_kumquat-muffins/</guid><description>I usually make muffins using butter milk. I did not have any and wanted to make muffins so I tried using cream cheese instead. It worked very well.
I think one could easily replace the kumquats with any other type of fruit or leave them out altogether.
Ingredients 1/2 cup margarine 1/2 cup sugar 3 eggs 1 tsp vanilla sugar 2 cups flour 1 tsp baking powder 100 g cream cheese 150 g kumquat Directions Chop the kumquats including peel, I used a food processor to do this.</description></item><item><title>Lentil paté</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-07-xx_lentil-pate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-07-xx_lentil-pate/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 onion 1 laurel leaf 3 cloves 350 g lentils (black) 800 ml vegetable broth 1 tsp oregano 2 tbsp olive oil some zest of a lemon salt, pepper 2 tbsp ground almonds 2 tbsp soy sauce With mustard carrots 1 carrot 20 g celery olive oil 2 tbsp coarse mustard salt, pepper cress On bread 2 rolls or a baguette cress Directions Peel the onion.</description></item><item><title>Lentil soup</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-08-xx_lentil-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-08-xx_lentil-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients oil 3 cloves of garlic 2 cm ginger 6 cardamom pods 1 tsp. yellow curry paste 300 g lentils 500 ml vegetable broth 400 ml coconut milk Directions Heat oil in pan. Cut garlic &amp;amp; ginger into small pieces. Saute ginger, garlic, and cardamom pods in the pan for 2 minutes. Add curry paste &amp;amp; lentils and fry briefly. Pour in the vegetable broth and coconut milk.</description></item><item><title>Marzipan Lemmings</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_marzipan-lemmings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_marzipan-lemmings/</guid><description>On my birthday I decided to make a lemming cake, so I made these cute figures out of marzipan.
I&amp;rsquo;m not quite happy with the way the hair turned out, it looks sort of like a helmet.
The next few pictures show the lemmings on the cake. Yum.</description></item><item><title>Mini Chocolate Cheesecake</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-08-xx_mini-chocolate-cheesecake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-08-xx_mini-chocolate-cheesecake/</guid><description>Ingredients 9 sheets of puff pastry 100 g chocolate (I used dark chocolate) 1 egg 70 g sugar 200 g cream cheese 1 tbsp. sour cream 1 tsp. lemon juice Directions Preheat the oven to 180°C. Butter 9 cupcake forms. Melt the chocolate and set aside. Cut each sheet of puff pastry into three pieces, roll them a little thinner and place them in the cupcake form. Beat the egg and the sugar until white.</description></item><item><title>Miso soup</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_miso-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_miso-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients 400 ml water 1 tsp. dashi-no-moto (powder) 1 shiitake mushroom 2 tbsp. miso paste (we used dark miso paste) 275 g silken tofu 2 scallions Directions Drain the tofu, then cut it into small pieces. Cut the shiitake in small pieces, place into a pot with 400 ml cold water and the dashi-no-moto and bring to a boil. When the water in the pot is boiling turn down the heat.</description></item><item><title>Oat bread</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_oat-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_oat-bread/</guid><description>For this bread, you have to start the day before you want to bake it. On that day, it only needs a few minutes. On the next day, it takes about 20 min to prepare and 45min to bake.
Ingredients 200g oat flakes 400ml buttermilk 2 tsp. baking powder 1/2 tsp. salt 250-300g flour Directions Soak the oat flakes in the buttermilk. Leave in the fridge over night.</description></item><item><title>Plantain Curry</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_plantain-curry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_plantain-curry/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 plantains
oil
3-4 scallions
1 yellow (bell) pepper
1 tbls. curry paste (yellow)
400 ml coconut milk
1 tbls. sugar
1 tbls. vinegar
4 tbls. fish sauce
3 cm ginger
1 tsp. coriander green
lemon grass
1 cup rice as side dish</description></item><item><title>Rosemary Rolls</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_rosmary-rolls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_rosmary-rolls/</guid><description>Ingredients 250 ml milk 1 tsp sugar 10 g fresh yeast 3 cups flour 1 tsp baking powder 1 tsp salt 1 tbsp oil 1 tbsp margarine rosemary sea salt Directions Mix the milk, yeast and sugar in small bowl and leave for about 30 minutes. Mix the flour, baking powder and salt. Add the yeast-mixture and stir well. Add the oil and knead the dough until it is smooth and does not stick to your hands anymore.</description></item><item><title>Scarborough Muffins</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_scarborough-muffins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_scarborough-muffins/</guid><description>Ingredients 125 g flour 50 g oats 40 g chopped walnuts 40 g chopped almonds 1 tsp baking powder 10 g fresh yeast 60 g yogurt 75 ml milk Directions In a large bowl mix flour, oats and chopped walnuts, chopped almonds and baking powder. In a small bowl mix yogurt, milk and yeast. Stir the two mixtures together and leave to rise for about 30 minutes. Preheat the oven to 180 °C.</description></item><item><title>Schweineohren / "Pig ears"</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-08-xx_schweineohren-pig-ears/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-08-xx_schweineohren-pig-ears/</guid><description>Base ingredients 3 live pigs 6 sheets of pastry dough Filling I (hearty) 200g feta cheese 100 g cream cheese with &amp;lsquo;erbs in it 3 green peperoni 1 clove of garlic 1 egg pepper Filling II (sweet) 75g ground hazelnuts 75g ground almonds 5 tbsp. honey 3 tbsp. cream Instructions Preheat the oven to 200°C. For Filling I, cut the peperoni and garlic into small pieces.</description></item><item><title>Scrambled Tofu</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_scrambled-tofu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_scrambled-tofu/</guid><description>Directions Go to http://www.theppk.com/recipes/dbrecipes/index.php?RecipeID=110 and do what it says. :D The only things we did differently were that we left out the mushrooms and the nutritional yeast (where can you get this stuff?). It was yummy none the less!
Especially the tummy-rubbing part was easy, because the amount was more than enough for the two of us and we were full for the rest of the day.
As the only side dish, we made some Guacamole</description></item><item><title>Spiced Soy Granulate for Tacos</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_taco-spices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_taco-spices/</guid><description>Spices 1 tsp oil 1 clove garlic 1 small onion 1/2 tsp cayenne pepper 1 tsp paprika 1/2 tsp cumin 1/2 tsp oregano Other Ingredients 1/2 l vegetable broth 300 g soy granulate or (carnivorous version):
500 g ground meat Directions Soak the soy granulate in the broth for half an hour. Meanwhile: Chop the onion and garlic. Heat oil in a pan and fry the onion and garlic briefly.</description></item><item><title>Spinach-feta pastries</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_spinach-feta-pastries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_spinach-feta-pastries/</guid><description>Ingredients 50 g Butter
10 g fresh yeast (or a packet dried yeast)
250 g flour
90 ml water
1/2 tsp salt
1/2 tsp sugar
250 g frozen, chopped spinach
100 g feta
2 cloves garlic
1 tbsp. creme fraiche
salt
pepper
Directions Defrost the spinach.</description></item><item><title>Stuffed paprika</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_stuffed-paprika/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_stuffed-paprika/</guid><description>We made one large paprika (ca. 350g) per person.
Ingredients (per paprika) 1 large bell paprika 2 slices toast 1 tsp. olive oil 1 clove garlic 1 tomato 100g goat cream cheese 2 tbsp. crème fraîche salt pepper basil (I used 2 tsp. chopped fresh basil) 1 tsp. oregano 1 tsp. thyme Instructions Cut the toast into small cubes and chop the garlic. Heat some olive oil in a pan and fry the toast until it is brown.</description></item><item><title>Tomato-Gorgonzola Pasta</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_tomato-gorgonzola-pasta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_tomato-gorgonzola-pasta/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 garlic clove 4-5 scallions (we only used the white parts) oil 250 g pasta (e.g. Penne) 125 ml whipping cream 125 ml milk 150 g Gorgonzola 2 tomatoes salt, pepper, oregano fresh basil a little grated Parmesan Directions Chop the scallions and garlic. Heat oil in a pan to medium heat. Add the garlic and the whites of the scallions. Fry for 1-2 minutes. Pour milk and whipped cream into the pan.</description></item><item><title>Tomato-Mozzarella Baguette</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-07-xx_tomato-mozzarella-baguette/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-07-xx_tomato-mozzarella-baguette/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 Coeur de Boeuf Tomato (or about 2-3 normal tomatoes) 1 package mozzarella 1 Baguette Olive oil salt, pepper basil Directions Heat up the baguette in the oven. Cut the tomato into slices. Put the tomato on the baguette and the mozzarella on top. Sprinkle with olive oil, salt, pepper, and basil.</description></item><item><title>Vegetable Patties</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_vegetable-patties/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_vegetable-patties/</guid><description>Ingredients 300 g zucchini 300 g carrots 2 onions 4 eggs 120 g flour 200 g cheese (Edamer) 60 g oats 2 tsp. parsley 2 tsp. curry powder 1 tsp. freshly ground pepper 4 tsp. paprika 1 tsp. salt oil Directions Chop the onions, zucchini and carrots finely. We use a food processor for this. Stir in the eggs, flour, oats and cheese. Add the seasoning generously. Heat a little oil in a pan.</description></item><item><title>Vinegar Potatoes</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/essig-kartoffeln/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/essig-kartoffeln/</guid><description>Ingredients 500 g Potatoes 50 ml vinegar essence 550 ml water 1 tsp salt pepper 2 tbsp oil Garnish Parsley (optional) Directions Slice the potatoes into thin rounds. Bring vinegar, salt and water to a boil in a pot and add the sliced potatoes. Boil for approximately 10-12 minutes until the potatoes are soft. In a frying pan heat up the oil and fry the potatoes until crisp.</description></item><item><title>Zucchini Gnocchi</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_zucchini-gnocchi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_zucchini-gnocchi/</guid><description>Ingredients 400 g gnocchi 2 tsp. oil 1 zucchini 3 large tomatoes (about 300 g) 1 onion 1 clove garlic 100 g feta 2 tsp. oregano 1 tsp. parsley 1tsp. thyme 1 tsp. salt 1/2 tsp. pepper Directions Chop the onions and the garlic finely. Cut the tomatoes and zucchini into about 2 cm cubes. Heat oil in a large pan. Fry the gnocchi in the pan briefly.</description></item></channel></rss>