<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>desert on Cucumber Sandwiches And Tea</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/tags/desert/</link><description>Recent content in desert on Cucumber Sandwiches And Tea</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/tags/desert/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Chocolate lava cake</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_chocolate-lava-cake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_chocolate-lava-cake/</guid><description>I accidentally stumbled across this recipe the other day and had to try it: Chocolate Lava Cake.
It tastes wonderful. I want to make it again, but I probably shouldn&amp;rsquo;t.</description></item><item><title>Congo Bars</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-06-xx_congo-bars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-06-xx_congo-bars/</guid><description>Ingredients 150 g butter, softened 3 eggs 200 g brown sugar (1 cup) 1 packet vanilla sugar (about 3 tsp.) 350 g flour (3 cups) 2 1/2 tsp. baking powder 1/2 teaspoon salt 100 g chocolate Directions Chop the chocolate finely. Preheat the oven to 180 °C. Combine butter, vanilla sugar and brown sugar using a mixer until blended. Add eggs, one at a time to sugar mixture, mixing on low in between each addition.</description></item><item><title>Cup-O'-Ccino</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_cup-o-ccino-with-liquid-chocolate-core/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_cup-o-ccino-with-liquid-chocolate-core/</guid><description>Ingredients 120 g margarine&amp;lt; 100 g sugar 2 eggs (large) 180 g flour 2 tsp. baking powder 6 tbsp. espresso 150 g chocolate Directions Chop 50 g of the chocolate into small pieces. Place margarine and sugar in a large bowl. Mix until fluffy. Add the eggs one by one, beating the mixture until it is smooth each time. Preheat the oven to 180° C. Mix the flour and baking powder and stir into the bowl.</description></item><item><title>Kumquat Muffins</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_kumquat-muffins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_kumquat-muffins/</guid><description>I usually make muffins using butter milk. I did not have any and wanted to make muffins so I tried using cream cheese instead. It worked very well.
I think one could easily replace the kumquats with any other type of fruit or leave them out altogether.
Ingredients 1/2 cup margarine 1/2 cup sugar 3 eggs 1 tsp vanilla sugar 2 cups flour 1 tsp baking powder 100 g cream cheese 150 g kumquat Directions Chop the kumquats including peel, I used a food processor to do this.</description></item><item><title>Mini Chocolate Cheesecake</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-08-xx_mini-chocolate-cheesecake/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-08-xx_mini-chocolate-cheesecake/</guid><description>Ingredients 9 sheets of puff pastry 100 g chocolate (I used dark chocolate) 1 egg 70 g sugar 200 g cream cheese 1 tbsp. sour cream 1 tsp. lemon juice Directions Preheat the oven to 180°C. Butter 9 cupcake forms. Melt the chocolate and set aside. Cut each sheet of puff pastry into three pieces, roll them a little thinner and place them in the cupcake form. Beat the egg and the sugar until white.</description></item></channel></rss>