<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vegan on Cucumber Sandwiches And Tea</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/tags/vegan/</link><description>Recent content in vegan on Cucumber Sandwiches And Tea</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/tags/vegan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Avocado Wasabi Salad</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_avocado-wasabi-salad/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_avocado-wasabi-salad/</guid><description>We found this delicious recipe for a salad: Avocado Wasabi Salad.
We didn&amp;rsquo;t have any broccoli the first time we made it, but it was still great. The amount of dressing is a bit much and we still have some in the fridge, so next time we&amp;rsquo;re probably only going to make half the dressing.</description></item><item><title>Guacamole</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_guacamole/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_guacamole/</guid><description>Ingredients 2 avocado (very ripe!) 6 tbsp. lime juice 2 tbsp. olive oil 2 cloves of garlic 1 onion salt &amp;amp; pepper chili powder 1 tomato Directions Peel the avocado. Place in a blender with 3 tbsp. lime juice and 1 tbsp. olive oil. Chop the garlic and onion. Also place in the blender. Add spices to taste. (salt, pepper, chili) Blend! Chop the tomato. Place in the blender.</description></item><item><title>Lentil soup</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-08-xx_lentil-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-08-xx_lentil-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients oil 3 cloves of garlic 2 cm ginger 6 cardamom pods 1 tsp. yellow curry paste 300 g lentils 500 ml vegetable broth 400 ml coconut milk Directions Heat oil in pan. Cut garlic &amp;amp; ginger into small pieces. Saute ginger, garlic, and cardamom pods in the pan for 2 minutes. Add curry paste &amp;amp; lentils and fry briefly. Pour in the vegetable broth and coconut milk.</description></item><item><title>Miso soup</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_miso-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_miso-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients 400 ml water 1 tsp. dashi-no-moto (powder) 1 shiitake mushroom 2 tbsp. miso paste (we used dark miso paste) 275 g silken tofu 2 scallions Directions Drain the tofu, then cut it into small pieces. Cut the shiitake in small pieces, place into a pot with 400 ml cold water and the dashi-no-moto and bring to a boil. When the water in the pot is boiling turn down the heat.</description></item><item><title>Scrambled Tofu</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_scrambled-tofu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_scrambled-tofu/</guid><description>Ingredients 250 g firm tofu 2 tbsp olive oil 3 cloves garlic (minced) 3 tbsp lime juice 1 carrot (grated) nutritional yeast Spice mix 2 tsp ground cumin 1 tsp dried thyme 1/2 teaspoon ground turmeric 1 teaspoon salt Directions In the oil fry up the spice mix, add garlic. Drain the tofu and kind of tear it apart and crumble it into the pan. Add the lime juice and some water if it seems too dry.</description></item><item><title>Spiced Soy Granulate for Tacos</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_taco-spices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_taco-spices/</guid><description>Spices 1 tsp oil 1 clove garlic 1 small onion 1/2 tsp cayenne pepper 1 tsp paprika 1/2 tsp cumin 1/2 tsp oregano Other Ingredients 1/2 l vegetable broth 300 g soy granulate or (carnivorous version):
500 g ground meat Directions Soak the soy granulate in the broth for half an hour. Meanwhile: Chop the onion and garlic. Heat oil in a pan and fry the onion and garlic briefly.</description></item><item><title>Vinegar Potatoes</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/essig-kartoffeln/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/essig-kartoffeln/</guid><description>Ingredients 500 g Potatoes 50 ml vinegar essence 550 ml water 1 tsp salt pepper 2 tbsp oil Garnish Parsley (optional) Directions Slice the potatoes into thin rounds. Bring vinegar, salt and water to a boil in a pot and add the sliced potatoes. Boil for approximately 10-12 minutes until the potatoes are soft. In a frying pan heat up the oil and fry the potatoes until crisp.</description></item></channel></rss>