<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>finger-food on Cucumber Sandwiches And Tea</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/tags/finger-food/</link><description>Recent content in finger-food on Cucumber Sandwiches And Tea</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/tags/finger-food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Congo Bars</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-06-xx_congo-bars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-06-xx_congo-bars/</guid><description>Ingredients 150 g butter, softened 3 eggs 200 g brown sugar (1 cup) 1 packet vanilla sugar (about 3 tsp.) 350 g flour (3 cups) 2 1/2 tsp. baking powder 1/2 teaspoon salt 100 g chocolate Directions Chop the chocolate finely. Preheat the oven to 180 °C. Combine butter, vanilla sugar and brown sugar using a mixer until blended. Add eggs, one at a time to sugar mixture, mixing on low in between each addition.</description></item><item><title>Cucumber Sandwiches</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_cucumber-sandwiches/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_cucumber-sandwiches/</guid><description>Step 1: Toast Ingredients 100 ml water 12 g fresh yeast 18 g salt 250 ml milk 500 g flour 2 tsp. baking powder 20 g sugar 20 g starch 30 g butter Directions In a small bowl mix water, yeast and salt. Stir well and leave for at least 30 minutes. I usually leave it overnight. Add the milk to the yeast mixture. In a large bowl mix the flour, baking powder, sugar, starch and butter.</description></item><item><title>Kumquat Muffins</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_kumquat-muffins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_kumquat-muffins/</guid><description>I usually make muffins using butter milk. I did not have any and wanted to make muffins so I tried using cream cheese instead. It worked very well.
I think one could easily replace the kumquats with any other type of fruit or leave them out altogether.
Ingredients 1/2 cup margarine 1/2 cup sugar 3 eggs 1 tsp vanilla sugar 2 cups flour 1 tsp baking powder 100 g cream cheese 150 g kumquat Directions Chop the kumquats including peel, I used a food processor to do this.</description></item><item><title>Scarborough Muffins</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_scarborough-muffins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_scarborough-muffins/</guid><description>Ingredients 125 g flour 50 g oats 40 g chopped walnuts 40 g chopped almonds 1 tsp baking powder 10 g fresh yeast 60 g yogurt 75 ml milk Directions In a large bowl mix flour, oats and chopped walnuts, chopped almonds and baking powder. In a small bowl mix yogurt, milk and yeast. Stir the two mixtures together and leave to rise for about 30 minutes. Preheat the oven to 180 °C.</description></item><item><title>Schweineohren / "Pig ears"</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-08-xx_schweineohren-pig-ears/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-08-xx_schweineohren-pig-ears/</guid><description>Base ingredients 3 live pigs 6 sheets of pastry dough Filling I (hearty) 200g feta cheese 100 g cream cheese with &amp;lsquo;erbs in it 3 green peperoni 1 clove of garlic 1 egg pepper Filling II (sweet) 75g ground hazelnuts 75g ground almonds 5 tbsp. honey 3 tbsp. cream Instructions Preheat the oven to 200°C. For Filling I, cut the peperoni and garlic into small pieces.</description></item><item><title>Spinach-feta pastries</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_spinach-feta-pastries/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_spinach-feta-pastries/</guid><description>Ingredients 50 g Butter
10 g fresh yeast (or a packet dried yeast)
250 g flour
90 ml water
1/2 tsp salt
1/2 tsp sugar
250 g frozen, chopped spinach
100 g feta
2 cloves garlic
1 tbsp. creme fraiche
salt
pepper
Directions Defrost the spinach.</description></item><item><title>Tomato-Mozzarella Baguette</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-07-xx_tomato-mozzarella-baguette/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-07-xx_tomato-mozzarella-baguette/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 Coeur de Boeuf Tomato (or about 2-3 normal tomatoes) 1 package mozzarella 1 Baguette Olive oil salt, pepper basil Directions Heat up the baguette in the oven. Cut the tomato into slices. Put the tomato on the baguette and the mozzarella on top. Sprinkle with olive oil, salt, pepper, and basil.</description></item></channel></rss>