<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>bread on Cucumber Sandwiches And Tea</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/tags/bread/</link><description>Recent content in bread on Cucumber Sandwiches And Tea</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/tags/bread/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cucumber Sandwiches</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_cucumber-sandwiches/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_cucumber-sandwiches/</guid><description>Step 1: Toast Ingredients 100 ml water 12 g fresh yeast 18 g salt 250 ml milk 500 g flour 2 tsp. baking powder 20 g sugar 20 g starch 30 g butter Directions In a small bowl mix water, yeast and salt. Stir well and leave for at least 30 minutes. I usually leave it overnight. Add the milk to the yeast mixture. In a large bowl mix the flour, baking powder, sugar, starch and butter.</description></item><item><title>Kaiser rolls</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_kaiser-rolls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_kaiser-rolls/</guid><description>Ingredients 250 ml water 10 g fresh yeast (or 1 packet dried yeast) 1 tsp sugar 1 tsp. salt 450 g flour 20 g butter 1 tbsp yoghurt (optional) 1 egg 3 tbsp. milk Directions Crumble the yeast into the water and mix until dissolved. Add the sugar and salt. Leave it for at least half an hour in a warm place. Place flour in a large mixing bowl.</description></item><item><title>Oat bread</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_oat-bread/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-03-xx_oat-bread/</guid><description>For this bread, you have to start the day before you want to bake it. On that day, it only needs a few minutes. On the next day, it takes about 20 min to prepare and 45min to bake.
Ingredients 200g oat flakes 400ml buttermilk 2 tsp. baking powder 1/2 tsp. salt 250-300g flour Directions Soak the oat flakes in the buttermilk. Leave in the fridge over night.</description></item><item><title>Rosemary Rolls</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_rosmary-rolls/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-04-xx_rosmary-rolls/</guid><description>Ingredients 250 ml milk 1 tsp sugar 10 g fresh yeast 3 cups flour 1 tsp baking powder 1 tsp salt 1 tbsp oil 1 tbsp margarine rosemary sea salt Directions Mix the milk, yeast and sugar in small bowl and leave for about 30 minutes. Mix the flour, baking powder and salt. Add the yeast-mixture and stir well. Add the oil and knead the dough until it is smooth and does not stick to your hands anymore.</description></item><item><title>Scarborough Muffins</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_scarborough-muffins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-05-xx_scarborough-muffins/</guid><description>Ingredients 125 g flour 50 g oats 40 g chopped walnuts 40 g chopped almonds 1 tsp baking powder 10 g fresh yeast 60 g yogurt 75 ml milk Directions In a large bowl mix flour, oats and chopped walnuts, chopped almonds and baking powder. In a small bowl mix yogurt, milk and yeast. Stir the two mixtures together and leave to rise for about 30 minutes. Preheat the oven to 180 °C.</description></item><item><title>Tomato-Mozzarella Baguette</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-07-xx_tomato-mozzarella-baguette/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-07-xx_tomato-mozzarella-baguette/</guid><description>Ingredients 1 Coeur de Boeuf Tomato (or about 2-3 normal tomatoes) 1 package mozzarella 1 Baguette Olive oil salt, pepper basil Directions Heat up the baguette in the oven. Cut the tomato into slices. Put the tomato on the baguette and the mozzarella on top. Sprinkle with olive oil, salt, pepper, and basil.</description></item></channel></rss>