<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>soup on Cucumber Sandwiches And Tea</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/tags/soup/</link><description>Recent content in soup on Cucumber Sandwiches And Tea</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/tags/soup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Courgette soup</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-07-xx_courgette-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-07-xx_courgette-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients 400g courgette 1 small onion 2 small potatoes olive oil 250 ml vegetable broth 3 tbsp lime juice (to taste) salt, pepper 250 ml butter milk Directions Cut the courgette, onion and small potatoes into small pieces. Heat the olive oil in a pan. Saute the onion in the olive oil briefly, then add courgette and potatoes. Add the vegetable broth and let simmer until the potatoes are soft.</description></item><item><title>Lentil soup</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-08-xx_lentil-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2012-08-xx_lentil-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients oil 3 cloves of garlic 2 cm ginger 6 cardamom pods 1 tsp. yellow curry paste 300 g lentils 500 ml vegetable broth 400 ml coconut milk Directions Heat oil in pan. Cut garlic &amp;amp; ginger into small pieces. Saute ginger, garlic, and cardamom pods in the pan for 2 minutes. Add curry paste &amp;amp; lentils and fry briefly. Pour in the vegetable broth and coconut milk.</description></item><item><title>Miso soup</title><link>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_miso-soup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cucumber-sandwiches.github.io/recipes/2010-02-xx_miso-soup/</guid><description>Ingredients 400 ml water 1 tsp. dashi-no-moto (powder) 1 shiitake mushroom 2 tbsp. miso paste (we used dark miso paste) 275 g silken tofu 2 scallions Directions Drain the tofu, then cut it into small pieces. Cut the shiitake in small pieces, place into a pot with 400 ml cold water and the dashi-no-moto and bring to a boil. When the water in the pot is boiling turn down the heat.</description></item></channel></rss>